https://jamaicapost.gov.jm/privacy-data/

Introduction
Protecting the privacy and personal information of our customers is of paramount importance and as such, we are committed to ensuring that there is no misuse of any personal or other data which may be collected from you.
This policy briefly explains why we collect, use and whenever necessary, disclose your personal information.
Why We Collect Your Information
Jamaica Post collects personal information from you only with your knowledge and consent and as may be required by law. We collect this information to allow you to purchase or register for certain products and services; to transact business online; to provide you with services or information that may be of interest to you; to facilitate online customer queries; and to continuously improve your experience when doing business with us.
The personal information we collect may include your name, email address, mailing or business address, phone numbers, credit card and other banking information but may include other information when needed to fulfill your requests and queries and as may be required by law.
We will only retain your personal information as long as it is necessary, including updating the product or service or as required by law. We do not however retain your credit card information.
When Is Your Information Disclosed?
Your personal information will only be disclosed with your authorization and as may be required by law.
Protecting Your Personal Information
We employ appropriate technical, administrative and physical procedures to protect your information from unauthorized disclosure, loss, misuse or alteration.
We use the industry standard encryption software, Secured Socket Layer (SSL) 128 bit encryption. The URL in your browser will change to “HTTPS” instead of “HTTP” when this security feature is invoked. Your browser may also display a lock symbol on its bottom task bar line to indicate this secure transmission is in place.
Loss of Personal Information
Despite our every effort to protect your personal information, there remains the possibility that a breach of our security could occur. In the event this occurs, we will:
seek to rapidly identify and secure the breach to prevent any further breaches;
engage the appropriate authorities where criminal activity is suspected;
notify the affected individuals directly if appropriate and where possible; and
if appropriate, place a notice on our website advising our customers of the breach.
Links from Jamaica Post Website
Our website may contain links to other websites. While we take measures to ensure that the links on our website are to reputable and well-established companies, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. We encourage you to read and understand the privacy policies on those websites prior to providing any information to them.
Cookies
Cookies are small data files that a website you visit may save on your computer or handheld device. Our website may use cookies for user authentication, keeping track of your preferences, promotional campaigns, tracking our audience size and traffic patterns, and in certain other cases.
You can configure your internet browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is sent. Most browsers accept cookies by default.
By simply visiting our website, you do not disclose, nor do we collect personal data about you. The information collected about your visit is limited to technical data such as:
the internet address (or IP address) of the device you used to access this website;
whether you reached the site using a search engine or if you clicked a link on another website;
the type of web-browser you used; and
the type of device you used to access the internet.
We may use this technical data for administrative and statistical purposes as well as to help us improve our website.
If you have any questions about our Website Security and Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact Jamaica Post at 1-888-526-7678 or e-mail your privacy concerns to info@jamaicapost.gov.jm .
Search for:
Copyright © 2014 Jamaica Postal Corporation. All Rights Reserved
